question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola's original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
